[{"answer": "Not married are you, Sergeant?  That's good, you get to fuck a few more. So how long you known my friend", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Did he get you the job", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "As she's a member of my staff, may I ask what this is about", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I see .. Well, she's teaching a", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "No way .. not me, Mister. I'm not going up there again. Might find someone's prick in a ho", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Forget it. They got stringent hy", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "How come the F.B.I. don't put anya this together? They wor", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Identity of whom? You got a girl, doesn't even have a driver's li", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "\"Thoughts that lie too deep for tears", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "No, my friend .. Do you like poetry", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I  heard you. You just don't like hearing . You got this whole damned thing outta proportion. I don't know what you gotten used to in that place, but I don't believe there's a Police Chief, , would put a task force together for a body part .", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "We have a body part in suspicious circumstances", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Flying colors ..", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I said it", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I have to talk to you, my friend", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You know? How do you know", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Oh, it was  that nearly ran into me", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I guess, more than usual this time of the year. My mother", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I may have said som", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Alright, I gave him the case? .. So the case is closed, so what", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Bull shit .. I'm in my prime .", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What d'you mean,", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "It was the only shot I had .", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "That's right. Except I'd deci", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I don't know. I wasn't thin", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I was unconscious 10 seconds ago", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Yeah, I could see. Then I ran. Climbed out of the window, ran down the fire escape, and right at the bottom, I found my friend .", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Sure I was breathless ..", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Sure I was breathless ..", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Not until I was in the hospital", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Like the flashlight?  Had you been drinking that night", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "That wasn't my question", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "My left hand", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "The  was in my right hand .", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I wanna be made aware of them ", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "There you go again?", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "You don't", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "The man who shot my friend,  it .", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "You didn't check", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "That wasn't my question", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Are you going up there", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "What about the man? .. Has he seen this? ..  .. Alright, make your call, and get up there ... Bullshit or not, I wanna proper statement .", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "I can't identify him .", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Then why didn't he kill me", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "You . And you got no voice in here, my friend, ", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I don't lie", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Under exceptional circumstances", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I never lied to my friend .", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "As I said, Sergeant, you nearly ran into ? What's the problem", "docId": "jennifer-eight-script.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "The van", "qsentId": 50}]